PATARAPONG CHAROENPOL

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

062-8696603

p.patarapong2000@gmail.com

13/2 Napa, Mueang Chon Buri,20000 Chon Buri

SKILLS

Javascript, Typescript, Golang, Python, HTML & CSS

React, NextJS, ElectronJS, NestJS, React Native

UI frameworks: Tailwind, Ant Design, Material UI

EDUCATION

Computer engineering

Suranaree university of technology

Sep 2018 - Mar 2022

Delved deeply into the realms of Web Programming, Algorithm and Data Structures, Machine Learning, Computer Vision, and Computer Network, achieving a GPA of 2.74.

LANGUAGES

Thai (Native)

English(Moderate)

PROFILE

With 2 years of experience, a Full Stack programmer is a professional who has skills in back-end and front-end software development and can implement most of the language and technology used in developing web applications most efficiently: he can work in a team and combines the language and technologies of modern development.

My dedication to developing high-quality software and incoming future fields is the qualification of a Full Stack programmer with sufficient experience to make your project a star.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full stack Developer

KASIKORN Business-Technology Group (Outsource)

Oct 2022 - Apr 2024

- Create a website through Next JS, React, and Electron JS, which is based on UX/UI and provided by the design team.
- Connect to the back-end through Axios, Fetch, and Socket.
- Build the system of the website, landing page, and back office according to the requirements of the customers.
- Create a database and create back-end system logic with NestJS gRPC and Prisma.
- A solution based on the requirements received by users is proposed.

Frontend Developer

Y.I.M Corporation, Bangkok

Nov 2021 - Oct 2022

- Create a Website through Next JS, React, and Electron JS is based on UX/UI and provided by the design team.
- · Connect to back-end through Axios, Fetch and Socket
- Create a mobile applications with React Native based on UX/UI and provided by the design team.
- Build the basic system of the website, landing page and back office according to the requirements of the customers.